Where'd I put the charger again?
Here.
Thanks.
Things have changed slightly between us
ever since that day,
a few months ago.
[2 Months Ago]
- Well...
You first.
No, go ahead.
I'm sorry.
I was overly harsh with you.
Call it a slip of the tongue.
I... told you to do what you wanted?
Oh, right.
It's fine, I wasn't bothered by that at all.
- At all?
- At all.
I see...
Yup.
- Haru...
- I must've put you on the spot.
I promise I won't ask again.
Huh?
Sorry I raised such a fuss about it.
See you later.
Take care.
Say, are you free this weekend?
- Huh?
- I mean...
The two of us don't really go out together.
Actually, if we exclude lunches and dinners,
our outings together total to zero.
You make a point.
So let's change that.
Or did you have plans?
I don't. This is so exciting!
Think of where you want to go, okay?
I will.
Our relationship has changed,
ever so slightly.
[Episode 9]
Hey there, Sensei.
- Don't call me that.
- Why not?
- You're releasing a book.
- Who would've thought, right?
A short story I posted online went viral,
and now it's going to be published.
That just proves how popular it became.
I suppose people enjoy risqué stories.
I mean, a one-night stand
with a male prostitute?
Now how'd you come up with that idea?
Erm, well... rather than come up with it...
I based the story off a friend of a friend.
Fascinating.
I'm that "friend", right?
You can't deny it.
Sorry.
To think you'd become a published author.
Your story reached 4.5 million views, right?
I was just as shocked.
I didn't realize my experience
would be such a hit sensation.
Which you couldn't own up to,
so you pinned it on a "friend".
Of course I couldn't!
How could I admit I almost had sex
with a male therapy-prostitute?
I see your point.
His name was Natsuo, right?
- Have you seen him since?
- No. I don't even know his number.
Don't you want to use
the condoms he gave you?
Well, I know I made a huge fuss about it,
but things are going well between Ouji and I.
Sure, we aren't intimate.
But I really don't mind.
I guess I just needed to release
my pent up sexual frustration.
Hasn't Ouji noticed a change?
He probably knows something happened.
He hasn't seen your story circulating around?
No! If he saw, it'd be over.
Thank god I posted it anonymously.
Won't your name be published
when it becomes a book?
I haven't even told him I'm an author.
So many secrets,
yet you say things are "going well".
I mean...
I think these secrets are actually helping.
Ouji seems like a secretive guy, right?
I suppose.
While I'm the complete opposite of that.
You certainly are.
So now that I'm hiding something,
he seems bothered by it.
What a roundabout way
of grabbing his attention.
I wasn't trying to get his attention.
It just happened as a result.
Retreating as an offensive move, I see.
"Move"?
It's nothing that tactical, really.
Should I give it a try?
It's not that I wanted to retreat.
But I can't retreat, as the customer.
Sorry, what are we talking about?
Me, of course.
There's no point in retreating
when I need to pay to see him.
Can't you ask to meet outside his shift?
I wish I could.
But that's rude to ask of a professional.
How complex.
Anyway, since I'd rather not try my luck,
I'll just cough up the money, and push.
I can only say, "good luck".
What about you, Fuyumi?
Getting that youthful essence?
Really, "essence"?
I was trying to be less direct about it.
Well, it didn't work.
So, how are things going with him?
[Hidamari Women's Clinic]
Huh? That silence, could it be...
You quit your affair?
Not so blunt, Akina!
He's been busy. I haven't seen him recently.
You must be feeling so lonely.
But that'll make your reunion
all the more invigorating.
I guess that's not a bad deal.
You never change, Akina.
Can we meet in the next couple weeks?
I need to tell you something.
What's up?
I went to the clinic the other day.
They say my uterine fibroids
are growing larger.
Uterine fibroids?
I've been suppressing them with medication
for the last couple years.
They're expanding quite a bit,
so the doctor said
I ought to consider surgery.
Surgery...
There are many types of procedures now.
They won't have to cut an incision
in my body for this one.
Then that's fine, right?
What?
Your health is my utmost priority.
Besides, one child is enough for us.
Enough?
What do you mean, "enough"?
"Enough"?
Why is that your decision to make?
It's my body, my life.
Why is he always so condescending with me?
I missed you!
Fuyumi, you've been avoiding me.
Well, I...
Have you had enough of this?
Of me?
No, of course not.
Then are you scared?
Well...
So am I.
If we're found out, it's all over.
But I'm more terrified of losing you.
Are you free next Thursday?
I have the day off for once,
and I want us to talk.
[Operation Date: February 27th, Friday]
Thursday is...
I'm free all day.
Visit me after work,
in the morning, whenever.
Sorry, I'll be busy.
Then how about Friday night?
I should wrap up early that day.
I can't do Friday, either.
I guess...
This is it for us then?
No, that's not it.
I have surgery on Friday,
and since Thursday is the day before, I...
Surgery?
Fuyumi, is everything okay?
Are you ill?
Do you need to sit?
Wait, there're no benches around.
Here, use my jacket.
No, it's really no big deal.
- But...
- I need to get some uterine growth removed.
The procedure ends in an hour,
and I'm only bedridden a few days.
So really, it's no big deal...
It is a big deal.
It is a big deal, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I never noticed.
You must be so anxious.
You must be terrified.
What can I do to help?
10,000 copies?
Yes, for the first print.
Really?
That's a bit much...
Don't worry about the numbers.
Shibuya will design a book cover that sells.
That's a lot of pressure
for a vague order, boss.
And Haru,
you'll write an exclusive short story.
- 100 pages will suffice.
- 100?
To incentivize people to buy your book.
The main story is only 120 pages.
You want me to double that?
Yes. Good luck!
Will you be able to manage
an extra 100 pages?
I'll have to.
I can't let this opportunity go to waste.
Haru, you've changed.
Huh?
You've become beautiful.
You think?
Yes, you have.
[That night has changed things
for the better.]
Nail clippers...
Where did I put them?
Toss your old condoms, and use these instead.
With your husband, another dude, or...
You've become beautiful.
No, absolutely not.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
- You're early.
- Yeah.
The guys from the record label
wanted to grab dinner,
so I let Suzuki and Tanaka handle that.
You didn't need to join them?
Nah, it was a sudden invite anyway.
I'm beat.
Want something to drink?
Wait, you didn't have dinner.
- I'll whip up something for you.
- Haru.
We can order something for us.
Have you given it any thought?
- Huh?
- Where you want to go for our outing.
How about a hot springs day trip?
Huh? A hot spring?
What? Would you rather not?
No, that's not it, but...
Then where do you want to go?
- Erm...
- Five.
Four.
- Three.
- Hold on!
Two.
- One.
- I know!
Wow!
They actually ate it!
A zoo? How old are you?
Zoos are always great for a date.
A date, is it?
That's what an outing
between a couple is called.
- Wow!
- Woah.
It came here!
Wow, it's so regal.
And big, too!
I played my heart out.
Same. I can't believe I'm already worn out.
Thanks. I had fun today.
Glad to hear it.
The boys and I are taking a trip next week,
before our concert.
Three days, two nights.
Really? That's so nostalgic.
I remember all your old band trips.
And I remember you'd always want to follow.
Promising you'd be helpful to have around.
I never did get to join one though.
Want to come along for once?
Huh?
The other two wouldn't mind.
They really seem to like you.
How'd you do that?
By changing you for the better?
You're not wrong there.
But I guess you'd have work, huh?
Yeah. I'd join if I didn't have
deadlines coming up.
Too bad.
I'm so tired.
Here's a coffee.
Thanks.
See you when I get back.
Take care, and good luck.
Thanks.
Guess I'll get writing, too.
[That night has changed things
for the better.]
That night has changed things for the better.
Though my husband would not even kiss me,
I was desperate to love him,
both in body and heart.
But my desperation
could not be attributed to effort.
No, that was an obsession.
Once I cut my body from the equation,
our cogs were set in motion once more.
And yet...
"Yet"?
"Yet", what?
I'm getting hungry.
Maybe I'll order delivery.
Or me, if you want.
And yet...
Life is not so simple.
For once you've opened a door,
you crave to see what lies beyond it.
What the heck am I even writing?
That was quick.
[Preview]